<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Hiring on Dong Gao</title>
    <link>https://donggao111.github.io/hiring/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hiring on Dong Gao</description>
    <image>
      <title>Dong Gao</title>
      <url>https://donggao111.github.io/images/papermod-cover.png</url>
      <link>https://donggao111.github.io/images/papermod-cover.png</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.151.1</generator>
    <language>zh-cn</language>
    <copyright>Dong Gao</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://donggao111.github.io/hiring/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Senior Quant Researcher</title>
      <link>https://donggao111.github.io/hiring/senior-quant-researcher/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://donggao111.github.io/hiring/senior-quant-researcher/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Location: Shanghai&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Firm Context&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A leading China-based quantitative fund with tens of billions RMB in AUM and a long-standing top-tier performance record.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The firm has demonstrated consistent alpha generation across multiple market cycles and operates with institutional-level capital discipline and risk management rigor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is now expanding into global equity markets and building out a dedicated systematic long/short platform. This hire will join at the formation stage of that global mandate.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HFT Quant Researcher</title>
      <link>https://donggao111.github.io/hiring/hft-quant-researcher-global-pay/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://donggao111.github.io/hiring/hft-quant-researcher-global-pay/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Location: Shanghai&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Firm Context&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of the most established and consistently top-performing quantitative funds in China.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The firm has maintained industry-leading performance since inception and operates at global standards in both research depth and capital efficiency.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Its High Frequency Trading platform is equity-focused, with expanding coverage across global equities markets.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. Platform Characteristics&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This platform stands out for three structural reasons:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven Performance Stability – Long-term leading track record, not short-cycle outperformance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Equity-Focused HFT Infrastructure – Deep expertise in high-frequency stock trading with production-grade execution systems.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Research-First Culture – Low internal friction, high research autonomy, and minimal administrative overhead.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The environment is known for strong talent density and an efficient, performance-oriented workflow.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine Learning Researcher</title>
      <link>https://donggao111.github.io/hiring/machine-learning-researcher/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://donggao111.github.io/hiring/machine-learning-researcher/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Location: Shanghai&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Firm Context&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A first-tier quantitative fund in China with a long-standing top-tier performance record and institutional-scale capital base.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The firm operates a research-driven platform with strong engineering integration and global-level compensation standards.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Within its Strategy Research Division, the firm is further expanding its Machine Learning research capability, with a dedicated long-term mandate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. Research Focus&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This role focuses on:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exploring frontier machine learning and deep learning methodologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advancing modeling frameworks for security price prediction&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bridging academic AI research with production-grade systematic trading applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The team emphasizes:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Technology Lead (Open to CTO)</title>
      <link>https://donggao111.github.io/hiring/technology-lead-open-to-cto/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://donggao111.github.io/hiring/technology-lead-open-to-cto/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Location: Hong Kong&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Firm Context&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A newly launching hedge fund platform in Hong Kong, backed by multi-billion USD capital commitments from leading Wall Street institutions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The fund will operate a global systematic equities strategy under a centralized book structure, initially focused on Asia and Europe.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is not an incremental expansion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is a full platform build — capital secured, infrastructure being formed, core team under construction.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The firm is currently assembling its early core Quant and technology leadership team, offering competitive economics and meaningful long-term upside aligned with platform growth.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
